This is not a game.
Game Night is a mystery, comedy, crime film directed by John Francis Daley.
Max and Annie's weekly game night gets kicked up a notch when Max's brother Brooks
arranges a murder mystery party -- complete with fake thugs and federal agents.
So when Brooks gets kidnapped, it's all supposed to be part of the game.
As the competitors set out to solve the case, they start to learn that
neither the game nor Brooks are what they seem to be.
The friends soon find themselves in over their heads as each twist leads to
another unexpected turn over the course of one chaotic night.
Max, played by Jason Bateman.
Annie, played by Rachel McAdams.
Brooks, played by Kyle Chandler.
Sarah, played by Sharon Horgan.
Ryan, played by Billy Magnussen.
Kevin, played by Lamorne Morris.
Game Night is a 2018 American black comedy action film directed by John
Francis Daley and Jonathan Goldstein and written by Mark Perez.
It stars Jason Bateman and Rachel McAdams and follows a group of friends whose game
night turns into a real-life mystery after one of them is kidnapped.
The film's supporting cast includes Billy Magnussen, Sharon Horgan,
Lamorne Morris, Kylie Bunbury, Jesse Plemons, Michael C.
Hall, and Kyle Chandler.
Warner Bros.
Pictures released the film on February 23, 2018.
It received positive reviews from critics and has
grossed $117 million worldwide.
Plemons was nominated for the Detroit Film Critics
Society Award for Best Supporting Actor.
The film explores themes of jealousy, husband wife
relationship, married couple, sarcasm, dark comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.